foreign
all right
the Vietnamese government and those
particularly in Ho Chi Minh City tattoo
for their great support for prudentials
thank all of you our customers for
coming here today and supporting
Prudential foreign
how many of you have got children
now I am very lucky I have one son who's
three years old and very very naughty uh
when he was born he was very really ill
and he was born not breathing and no
heart and he was very very lucky to be
alive
ambulance came and took him to hospital
and he was on life support machine for
one week to keep him alive
the only thing you want to do as a
father is to protect your child and your
wife
now he's very lucky because I have
insurance
and I could worry and support my family
in the time when they may see me and not
have to worry about anything else
come here
I was very very lucky that I had
insurance and now my son runs around
breaking things keeping me up at night
but it's all worth it
so I'm very glad I had insurance
so Prudential day is an opportunity for
us to thank you our customers
and to also give an opportunity to share
what we have done throughout the last
year
it's also a great opportunity for us to
listen to our customers and see what we
continue to be a better company
um
I just very quickly like to share some
of our business results from 2011.
grew up 14 cents
with a new record of 1
397 billion Vietnamese
12 to 6 000 billion Vietnamese
investment was
2872 billion being resolved between 28
last year and I'll tell you you got
quieter
much thank you all for giving us the
support to have such impressive results
year on year since we've been here in
Vietnamese
and on this occasion I would like to
also announce a special bonus of 430
billion Vietnamese soldiers we're giving
to 104 000 customers
this is the second time you've had this
opportunity to give back and thank our
customers
in 2007 we're able to get back 521
billion Vietnamese up to 740 000
customers
and it's a great pride for all of us in
Prudential Vietnam to be able to give
back to our customers oh no no no no no
no no no no no no no yeah
I hope you enjoy Prudential day
I hope you share with us your thoughts
and feelings and I wish you all the
success happiness in the future but um